Von Tilzer / Gumm Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 11-45)
  - Vocal Music, Manuscripts (Box 11-25)
    - Lion, Male quartet (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Listen to the anvil chorus (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Little bit - I'll say so (Box-folder 18/26)
    - A little bundle from heaven (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Little devil Vincent, Text (Box-folder 18/28)
    - A little German heaven (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Liza (Box-folder 18/30)
    - Lollypop, Text (Box-folder 18/31)
    - London town Sam Howe (Box-folder 18/32)
    - Long Island Sound, Piano; parts (Box-folder 18/33)
    - Long long way to U.S.A., Piano (Box-folder 18/34)
    - Long way Peerless 4, Vocal quartet (Box-folder 18/35)
    - Look at me now and the day you got me, Text (Box-folder 18/36)
    - Look who's here (Waltz) Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 18/37)
    - Looking hot and keeping cool, Text (Box-folder 18/38)
    - Lost a girl (Box-folder 18/39)
    - The lost chord blues, Text (Box-folder 18/40)
    - Lovable rogue, Text (Box-folder 18/42)
    - Love, Vocal quartet, quintet (Box-folder 18/43)
    - Love is such a tender feeling, Piano; text (Box-folder 18/44)
    - Love love love (Box-folder 18/45)
    - Love me Palais Royal (Box-folder 18/46)
    - Love me, love my dog (no. 3), Text (Box-folder 18/47)
    - Love me nice [slumming] Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Parts; text (Box-folder 18/48)
    - L-O-V-E spells love Duncan Sisters, Piano; text (Box-folder 18/49)
    - Love time (Box-folder 18/50)
    - Love will find (Box-folder 18/51)
    - Lovin' Sam (Box-folder 18/52)
    - Lucky girl (Box-folder 18/53)
    - Mad Ma-Madeline Louis Dacre, Text (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Maggie McCart (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Maggie spill the beans (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Mah-jong, Piano (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Maiden's prayer (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Makim's, Female quartet (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Man behind the hammer and saw (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Mandy Stock, arranged by Smalle, Male quartet (Box-folder 19/8)
    - March Nick-o-demus, Saxophone trio (Box-folder 19/9)
    - March song Mossinger (Box-folder 19/10)
    - March two step (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Marie (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Mariutcha, Piano (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Mary (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Maybe for someone but not for you, Text (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Me & myself Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Meanest man (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Medleys, Piano; [texts] (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Meet me at the ball tonight (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Meet me at the Waldorf (Box-folder 19/29)
    - Mirror Dan Sullivan, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 19/30)
    - Mickey Slater singing waiter Norworth, Piano; lead sheet; text (Box-folder 19/31)
    - Million reasons (Box-folder 19/32)
    - Miserary Henry Troy & Al Johns, Piano (Box-folder 19/33)
    - Miss Angelina Snow Jas T. Bryum (Box-folder 19/34)
    - Miss Tammany (Box-folder 19/35)
    - Mississippi shore, Text (Box-folder 19/36)
    - Mistakes will happen (Box-folder 19/37)
    - Mister G. (Box-folder 19/38)
    - Mobile Sam, banjo man (Box-folder 19/39)
    - Moon (Box-folder 19/40)
    - Moonlight night (Box-folder 19/41)
    - Mosquito & the frog Whiting Burt (Box-folder 19/42)
    - Mother Ad Hoyt; Bison City 4; Rover, Piano; mixed quartets (Box-folder 19/43)
    - Mother could only see me (Box-folder 19/44)
    - Move up closer to me, kid (Box-folder 19/45)
    - Mr. Booze man (Box-folder 19/46)
    - Mr. Joy May Ward, Piano; parts (Box-folder 19/47)
    - Mum's the word, 1st violin part (Box-folder 19/48)
    - Music is playing (Box-folder 19/49)
    - Music russle of the skirt [slumming] (Box-folder 19/50)
    - My bagpipe Sandy, Text (Box-folder 19/51)
    - My birthday (Box-folder 19/52)
    - My chop suey girl A. Roattino, 1st violin part (Box-folder 19/53)
    - My Dixie Lou Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 19/54)
    - My Dixie queen (Box-folder 19/55)
    - My girl (Box-folder 19/56)
    - My love to Nellie (Box-folder 19/57)
    - My mamma dear (Box-folder 19/58)
    - My old man had a funny little walk, Piano; text (Box-folder 19/59)
    - My ragtime boy (Box-folder 19/60)
    - My sweet American rose Alice W. Melville; arranged by Samuel Perlstein, Piano; text (Box-folder 19/61)
    - My sweet babee, Text (Box-folder 19/62)
    - My sweet one (Box-folder 19/63)
    - My sweetheart Amy Ashmore Clark, Sam Siebert, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 19/64)
    - My sweetie Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 19/65)
    - Nasty disposition (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Nationals, Piano; lead sheet (Box-folder 20/2)
    - 'Neath an Indian summer moon Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (with guitar); text (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Never knew, Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Never too late (Box-folder 20/5)
    - A nice little girl is naughty, Text (Box-folder 20/6)
    - No one knew just what she wanted, only me (Box-folder 20/7)
    - No[one] loves a thin man (Box-folder 20/8)
    - No use asking me why (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Nobody but Abie shall do it Edward Clark, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Nobody else but you (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Nobody knows what a little love (Box-folder 20/12)
    - None of my business (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Northern blue and gray of Dixie, Text (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Not enough love, baby Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Nothin' but you (Box-folder 20/16)
    - Nothing more to say Charlotte Parry (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Nothing new (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Now I know (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Nurse song (Box-folder 20/20)
    - O-O-O-O-O-O'Brien, Text (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Off the bunk Joe Herbert (Box-folder 20/22)
    - Officer (Box-folder 20/23)
    - Oh Daddy come home (Box-folder 20/24)
    - Oh dear (Box-folder 20/25)
    - Oh how I love you (Box-folder 20/26)
    - Oh Marie (Box-folder 20/27)
    - Oh, oh, Miss Lucy Ella (1907) Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 20/28)
    - Oh! Such a lovin' feeling [also known as Head over heels in love] (Box-folder 20/29)
    - Oh what a beautiful dream (Box-folder 20/30)
    - Oh what a summer (Box-folder 20/31)
    - Oh what a wonderful dream (Box-folder 20/32)
    - Oh what I could do (Box-folder 20/33)
    - Oh, what I'd do for you, Text (Box-folder 20/34)
    - Old B'way (Box-folder 20/35)
    - Old jay (Box-folder 20/36)
    - Old King Solomon (Box-folder 20/37)
    - On the B & O (Box-folder 20/38)
    - On the Champs-Elysées, Text (Box-folder 20/39)
    - On the day that comes before Monday, Text (Box-folder 20/40)
    - On the level Barry (Box-folder 20/41)
    - Once was enough for me (Box-folder 20/42)
    - 100 years ago Harry Von Tilzer; Billy Gould, Piano (Box-folder 20/43)
    - 100 years from now Bergeron (Box-folder 20/44)
    - Oola, Piano (Box-folder 20/45)
    - Open gates of paradise, Piano (Box-folder 20/46)
    - Open up (Box-folder 20/47)
    - Open up that door and let me in (Box-folder 20/48)
    - Opened my eyes (Box-folder 20/49)
    - Opera Taylor & Francis (Box-folder 20/50)
    - Operatic waltz song (Box-folder 20/51)
    - Opium, Piano (Box-folder 20/52)
    - Orange blossom time in California, Piano; drum part (Box-folder 20/53)
    - Organ begins to play (Box-folder 20/54)
    - Over here and over there Billy Curtis, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 20/55)
    - Pal (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Parcel post (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Part of it is mine Arthur Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Party wire Nordstrom & Potter, Piano (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Peek-a-boo (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Pick Mrs. Jack Sydney; B. B. 4, Mixed quartet; female quartet; lead sheet (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Pick on me Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Pick a nice one out for me Jos. H. McKeon, W. Raymond Walker, Harry M., Piano; Text (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Picture, Female quartet (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Pies, Piano (Box-folder 21/10)
    - A plain girl (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Play McCormick & Irving (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Polly (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Poor little me (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Poor old moon (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Potatoes Peerless 4, Male quartet (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Presents (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Pretty girl, Male quartet (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Pretty please (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Production (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Put the moon to bed (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Quaker, Piano (Box-folder 21/22)
    - Quaker song (Box-folder 21/23)
    - Quaker town (Box-folder 21/24)
    - Queen of fashion Sam Howe (Box-folder 21/25)
    - Racket song (Box-folder 21/26)
    - Ragtime boat (Box-folder 21/27)
    - Ragtime glider (Box-folder 21/28)
    - Ragtime wagon of love (Box-folder 21/29)
    - Rain, Piano (Box-folder 21/30)
    - Rainbow Jos. Morris, Male trio (Box-folder 21/31)
    - Regular pal (Box-folder 21/32)
    - Rib Singer & Jay (Box-folder 21/33)
    - Roaming (Box-folder 21/34)
    - Rock me (Box-folder 21/35)
    - The rocking chair brigade, Text (Box-folder 21/36)
    - Rocking in a ragtime boat (Box-folder 21/37)
    - Roll them bones (Box-folder 21/38)
    - Rolling stone (Box-folder 21/39)
    - Romeo Billie Darval, Jimmie Morgan (Box-folder 21/40)
    - Rose (Box-folder 21/41)
    - Rose Marie (waltz) (Box-folder 21/42)
    - Rose of my heart Ben Bernard (Box-folder 21/43)
    - Rosie (Box-folder 21/44)
    - Rube band (Box-folder 21/45)
    - Ruby Thorne (Box-folder 21/46)
    - Rug around the moon (Box-folder 21/47)
    - Safety first Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Sally simple (Box-folder 22/2)
    - The same as the night before (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Same sweet girl, Cello part (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Santa Claus (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Sardinia Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; piano; printed proofs; text (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Say, ain't it grand Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Says I to myself Midgie Miller, Piano; male quartet; text (Box-folder 22/8)
    - School days Boland & Knight (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Seadrift, Text; musical cues (Box-folder 22/10)
    - See it that way, Parts (3) (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Seeing Polly home (Box-folder 22/12)
    - See saw (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Semi-classic song (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Send you a picture, Male quartet (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Señorita (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Shadowland (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Shady side Broadway (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Shake 'em up (at Lucinda's Honolulu ball), Text (Box-folder 22/19)
    - She got off (Box-folder 22/20)
    - She hates me to go away Dyson (Box-folder 22/21)
    - The sheriff's going to get 'em (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Shylock (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Sicky sigh (Box-folder 22/24)
    - Since Tilly started taking Tastyeast (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Sing (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Sit down, stand up, walk around... Arranged by Dave Kaplan, Piano; parts (2) (Box-folder 22/27)
    - Sitting up with a sick friend (Box-folder 22/28)
    - Sleeping, Text (Box-folder 22/29)
    - Sleepy moon Marion Chase, Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/30)
    - Small world Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer; Sterling 3, Piano; male trio (Box-folder 22/31)
    - Smoke goes up the chimney, Text (Box-folder 22/32)
    - Snap your fingers (Box-folder 22/33)
    - Sneeze Geo. Mack, Piano (Box-folder 22/34)
    - Snowman Jesse Greer; Rice & Francis, Drum part (Box-folder 22/35)
    - Soldier's rosary (Box-folder 22/36)
    - Some day (Box-folder 22/37)
    - Some day sweet heart (Box-folder 22/38)
    - Some girl (Box-folder 22/39)
    - Some little girl Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 22/40)
    - Somebody loves you [also known as I love you both] Sabel (Box-folder 22/41)
    - Somebody's waiting Nonette, Chorus; male quartet; duet (Box-folder 22/42)
    - Someone, Text (Box-folder 22/43)
    - Someone I love (Box-folder 22/44)
    - Someone's more lonesome than you (Box-folder 22/45)
    - Something's going to happen De Noyer, Piano; parts; text (Box-folder 22/46)
    - The song that stole... (Box-folder 22/47)
    - Song to the chief, Text (Box-folder 22/48)
    - The song wasn't written that way Milt Feiber, Jess Feiber, Piano (Box-folder 22/49)
    - Sorry John Meyers (Box-folder 22/50)
    - Spank! Spank! Spank! Harry Von Tilzer, Texts (Box-folder 22/51)
    - Spellbound, Text (Box-folder 22/52)
    - Spoon with the man in the moon (Box-folder 22/53)
    - Squirrel & nut (Box-folder 22/54)
    - Stand up, sit down, walk around... Weston & Leon, Piano (Box-folder 22/55)
    - Standing on the corner (Box-folder 22/56)
    - Stolen sweets (waltz) Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Stop!, Piano (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Strolling along (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Studio Sam Howe (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Sue dear Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Sullivan's chowder party (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Sunday, Text (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Sunny Seville Sam Howe (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Sure and it's me that knows, Text (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Sweet little girl (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Sweet potatoes, Piano [partial] (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Sweeta-Marie (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Sweeter (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Sweeties Pell & Pell; Woodrow, Vocal quartets; violin part (Box-folder 23/14)
    - 'Tain't none of my business Cecil Mack & Chris. Smith, Piano-vocal; text (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Take an aspirin, Piano; text (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Take it from me, Piano (Box-folder 23/17)
    - Take me along (Box-folder 23/18)
    - Take me where the music is playing (Box-folder 23/19)
    - Taking care of mother (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Tax on love, Quartet (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Tear League of Nations, Male quartet (with words); quintet (Box-folder 23/22)
    - Tear is a smile Sterling Trio (Box-folder 23/23)
    - Tell Mamie I said good-bye Billy Curtis, Text (Box-folder 23/24)
    - Ten cent store (Box-folder 23/25)
    - Ten-fifty nine (Box-folder 23/26)
    - Tennessee medley, Piano (Box-folder 23/27)
    - Thanks goodnight (Box-folder 23/28)
    - That old-fashioned garden back home, Text (Box-folder 23/29)
    - That what you call love [also known as You're too good to lose] (Box-folder 23/30)
    - That's going some (Box-folder 23/31)
    - That's why Bluebeard's beard turned blue Billy Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer, Piano-vocal; text; gags for "Bluebeard" (Box-folder 23/32)
    - There isn't anyone with strings on me (Box-folder 23/33)
    - There'll be someone waiting for you (Box-folder 23/34)
    - They never come back George McFadden (Box-folder 23/35)
    - They're after me, Piano (Box-folder 23/36)
    - 36 inches Costello & Heinzman[?] (Box-folder 23/37)
    - Tina waltzes Alberto Rizzi, Piano (Box-folder 23/38)
    - To the music of the band (Box-folder 23/39)
    - To the tune of a beautiful song, Text (Box-folder 23/40)
    - Tokio (Box-folder 23/41)
    - Tonight's the night (Box-folder 23/42)
    - Top o' the mornin' Joe Maxwell, Chorus (Box-folder 23/43)
    - Tra-la-la (Box-folder 23/44)
    - Tra-la-la-la la (Box-folder 23/45)
    - Trail of yesterday K & S; Walter (Box-folder 23/46)
    - Trench fires, Piano; quartet (Box-folder 23/47)
    - Twas a braw brecht moonlecht necht Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 23/48)
    - Tweet, tweet (Box-folder 23/49)
    - Twelve o'clock fellow La Rue; Tom Brown, Chorus; quartet (Box-folder 23/50)
    - Twist Kilgour (Box-folder 23/51)
    - Two (2) arms (Box-folder 23/52)
    - Ukalou, Piano; melody/words (Box-folder 23/53)
    - Umpah (Box-folder 23/54)
    - Uncle Sammy, Text (Box-folder 23/55)
    - Under love's moon Duncan Sisters, Piano (Box-folder 23/56)
    - Under the Hudson River (Box-folder 23/57)
    - Under the weeping willow tree, Piano; text (Box-folder 23/58)
    - Under the Yiddish moon (Box-folder 23/59)
    - U.S.A. (Box-folder 23/60)
    - A vagabond am I Harry Von Tilzer, Text (Box-folder 24/1)
    - The villain (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Violets (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Waiting, Female quartet (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Waltz (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Waltzing, Text (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Wasn't my fault (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Wasn't that thoughtful of him (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Watchful waiting, Piano (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Waves rolled on (Box-folder 24/10)
    - We go for a lark on the tail of a shark, Text (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Wedding breakfast (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Wee! wee! wee!, Text [partial] (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Welcome to our city, Kitty (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Well worth waiting for, Piano (Box-folder 24/15)
    - What a fool I'd be (Box-folder 24/16)
    - What a uniform (Box-folder 24/17)
    - What are you getting from somebody else? (Box-folder 24/18)
    - What are you going to do for me, Text (Box-folder 24/19)
    - What could I do (Box-folder 24/20)
    - What do I care (Box-folder 24/21)
    - What do you want of my young life?, Text (Box-folder 24/22)
    - What you've started Dreyer & Fay, Text (Box-folder 24/23)
    - What's goin' to be the outcome if the income don't come in?, Piano-vocal (without words); text (Box-folder 24/24)
    - When Anna practices on her "pianner", Text (Box-folder 24/25)
    - When Casey marched away (Box-folder 24/26)
    - When I gave myself to you, Text (Box-folder 24/27)
    - When I went to school [slumming] (Box-folder 24/28)
    - When I'm with you, Piano (Box-folder 24/29)
    - When the golden rod is waving... John Meyer, Vocal parts with words (3) (Box-folder 24/30)
    - When you go to Picadilly pick a girl for me, Piano; text (Box-folder 24/31)
    - When you waltz with the girl you love, Piano-vocal (Box-folder 24/32)
    - Where are songs Barry 3 (Box-folder 24/33)
    - Where do [you] get that stuff? Celia Weston (Box-folder 24/34)
    - Where is she now? (Box-folder 24/35)
    - Where the morning glories... (Box-folder 24/36)
    - Where the rolling sea (Box-folder 24/37)
    - Whether it rains, whether it shines, Text (Box-folder 24/38)
    - Whistle Kilgour (Box-folder 24/39)
    - Who bribed the umpire Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 24/40)
    - Who hit McAdoo? Harry Von Tilzer, Piano; text (Box-folder 24/41)
    - Who puts me in my little bed (Box-folder 24/42)
    - Whoa January Schram & Raymond, Quartets (Box-folder 24/43)
    - Whoop de-doodle doodle do George Totten Smith (Box-folder 24/44)
    - Who's your lady friend (Box-folder 24/45)
    - Why did you (Box-folder 24/46)
    - Why do they play? (Box-folder 24/47)
    - Why do your kisses taste so sweet (Box-folder 24/48)
    - Why must you go, Text (Box-folder 24/49)
    - The widow [also known as U. S. A.], Piano; 1st violin part (Box-folder 24/50)
    - Wilhelmina Harry Von Tilzer, Piano (Box-folder 24/51)
    - Winter-time Meredith, Text (Box-folder 24/52)
    - Wireless Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 24/53)
    - The wireless telephone Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer, 1st violin parts (2); text (Box-folder 24/54)
    - A wonderful night to dream, Piano; text (Box-folder 24/55)
    - Won't go home till morning Delmore (Box-folder 24/56)
    - Won't someone find me a sweetheart Melvin M. Franklin, Piano (Box-folder 24/57)
    - Words & music (Box-folder 24/58)
    - The Yanks did it Van and Schenck; James Irving, Lead sheet (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Ye ne'er can tell until ye try, Piano-vocal [without words] (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Yiddisha Japanese Sam Howe (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Yo San, Parts (Box-folder 25/4)
    - You (Box-folder 25/5)
    - You are not the same sweet girl, Text [musical fragment only] (Box-folder 25/6)
    - You certainly opened my eyes [also known as Down where the cotton bud grows] (Box-folder 25/7)
    - You don't know what it is? (Box-folder 25/8)
    - You don't know what you're missing when you're not in love (Box-folder 25/9)
    - You haven't known me long enough for that, Text (Box-folder 25/10)
    - You needn't think I'm goin to do it all (Box-folder 25/11)
    - You took the sweet from sweetheart, Piano; lead sheet (Box-folder 25/12)
    - You'll never miss what you've never had, Text (Box-folder 25/13)
    - You're just a bad, bad baby Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer; arranged by Anthony J. Franchim[?], Piano-vocal (with ukelele) (Box-folder 25/14)
    - You're just a part of my heart, Piano; text (Box-folder 25/15)
    - You're my little theme song (Box-folder 25/16)
    - You're not with your Billy tonight Billy K. Wells, Al Stedman, Piano; text (Box-folder 25/17)
    - You're too good to lose (Box-folder 25/18)
    - Openings (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Untitled music, (3 folders) (Box-folder 25/20-22)
  - Vocal Music, Printed, 1878-1940 (Box 26)
    Contains printed piano-vocal scores, with music by Harry Von Tilzer and others.
    - Adieu Foulard adieu Madras, undated Claude-François Amour (Box-folder 26/1)
    - All aboard for Blanket Bay, 1910 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/2)
    - A bird in a gilded cage, 1900, 1927 Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Be my little honey bee (proofs), 1921 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Cubalita, 1941 Harry Sims, Alberto Rizzi (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Down on the farm, 1902, 1930 Raymonde A. Browne, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Emmet's lullaby, 1878 J. K. Emmet (Box-folder 26/7)
    - The girl I left before I left..., [cover pages only] (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Gliding through the old stage door, 1912 William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/9)
    - A hair of the dog that bit you, 1909 Vincent Bryan, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Harry Von Tilzer's Folio no. 3 for mandolin, guitar & piano, undated Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Harry Von Tilzer's old time favorite hits, 1922 Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/12)
    - He went a-hunting, 1907 Jack Mahoney, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/13)
    - The highly important fly [from The Jolly Baron], 1903 Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/14)
    - I don't care if there's a girl there [also known as Anywhere will do [and] Won't you waltz `The Merry Widow waltz' with me?], 1908 Charles Collins, R. P. Weston (Box-folder 26/15)
    - I don't want any other sweetheart... 1911 Jack Gorman, Andrew Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/16)
    - I might be coaxed, dear, but not by you, 1915 Jack Mahoney, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/17)
    - I want a girl just like the girl... 1911, 1938 William Dillon, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/18)
    - I wish I could hear you calling me now, undated Katharine Bainbridge, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/19)
    - I'm homesick, 1906 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/20)
    - In the eternal city, 1902 Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/21)
    - It's a hundred to one you're in love, 1916 Lou Klein, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/22)
    - Just across the river on the hill, 1934 Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/23)
    - Just around the corner, 1925 Dolph Singer, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/24)
    - Let's see, um, um, that's right, 1911 George Whiting, Andrew Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/25)
    - Little curly hair in a high chair [from Forty Little Mothers], 1940 Charles Tobias, Nat Simon (Box-folder 26/26)
    - Little skipper, 1939 Nick Kenny, Charles Kenny (Box-folder 26/27)
    - Maydee [from The Jolly Baron], 1903 Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/28)
    - My black Bess, 1898 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/29)
    - My counterfeit Bill, 1911 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/30)
    - Oh! Marjory! [from The Jolly Baron], 1903 Arthur J. Lamb, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/31)
    - On a Sunday afternoon, 1902, 1929 Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/32)
    - The pickaninny's paradise, 1918 Sam Ehrlich, Nat Osbourne (Box-folder 26/33)
    - The ragtime wagon of love, 1912 William Jerome, Harry Von Tilzer (Box-folder 26/34)